Kirill Gelvan

O Kirili4ik

STATEMENT

I am a new grad from BCs Applied Mathematics and Computer Science. Currently I am practising Deep Learning in side projects and spreading the knowledge to others with a lot of motivation and initiative, what ends up being a great experience for me. In my opinion best results can be achieved only by working in a team, with effective communication and confident leadership.

EDUCATION

Sept. 2017 - June 2021

Bachelor of Computer Science, GPA: 8.1/10.0

- Major: Applied Mathematics and Computer Science
- Selected courses: DL, DL for Audio, NLP, GANs, Large Scale ML National Research University Higher School of Economics, Moscow

Projects and Experience

July 2020 - July 2021

A study of Transformers for symbolic mathematics

- Wrote a bachelor thesis researching ways to utilize structure of math expressions in the Transformer architecture
- Used Python, Pytorch, Docker Samsung-HSE laboratory

Nov. 2019 - June 2020

Natural Language to Machine Learning corpus

- Designed and developed a corpus of queries in natural language matched with ML code snippets fulfilling the queries (>100k pairs)
- Used Python, Tensorflow, NLTK, Spacy Lambda-HSE laboratory

.

Sep. 2019 - Dec. 2019

Collembolas database

- Created a database from raw data to structure and facilitate data storage and processing for biologists
- Used PostgreSQL

A.N. Severtsov Institute of Ecology and Evolution RAS, G.-A. University Goettingen, Germany

TEACHING EXPERIENCE

Sep. 2021 - Present

Leading practical sessions on Deep Learning using Pytorch HSE Introduction to Deep Learning

Feb. 2020 - Present

Creating and managing DS, ML and DL online courses HSE Introduction to DS, Introduction to ML, Modern ML methods

Sept. 2019 - July 2021

Working as a teaching assistant on Machine Learning intensives Sherbank Corporate University, Higher School of Economics

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming: Python, SQL, C++, C

ML/DL: PyTorch, NumPy, SciPy, pandas, scikit-learn,

Spark, TensorFlow, Keras

Applications: git, bash, LATEX